COLLEEN "CED" MCCANN

User Experience & Marketing Designer

Chicago, IL

Austin, TX

colleen.ced.mccann@gmail.com

cedmccann.github.io/me/

linkedin.com/in/colleencedmccann/

PROFILE

Graphic designer, web developer, and Chicago native. Graduated from Arizona State University in May 2023 with a Bachelor's Degree in Graphic Information Technology. Approaches challenges using the design thinking methodology, and views every experience as an opportunity to grow.

EXPERIENCE

- Freelance UI/UX, Web, and Marketing Designer (May 2023-Present)
- Starbucks Barista (May 2022-December 2023)
- GameStop Senior Guest Advisor (June 2018-January 2020)
- Freelance Graphic Designer (2019-2020)

EDUCATION

- Arizona State University (Graduated May 2023): Bachelor's Degree in Graphic Information Technology
 - 4.0 GPA
 - Primary Focus: Web Design & Development
 - Secondary Focus: Computer Systems
- Illinois Institute of Technology (2 years): Majored in Computer Science
 - 3.5 GPA

SKILLS

- Adobe Creative Suite: InDesign, Photoshop, After Effects
- Figma
- Marketing & Brand Design
- AI Tools: Adobe Firefly
- Information Design
- Interaction Design
- Design Accessibility
- Experience Analytics: Google Analytics, Adobe Analytics
- User Research & Personas
- Front-End Development
- HTML5 & CSS
- JavaScript: jQuery, AJAX, RESTful APIs, JSON
- Search Engine Optimization (SEO)
- WordPress
- Adaptive & Responsive Design

RELEVANT Coursework

- Design Operations & Digital Workflow
- Multimedia Design, Planning, and Storyboarding
- Information Design and Usability
- Advanced Web Markup and Scripting
- Multimedia Authoring, Scripting, and Production
- Web Design and Web Content Design
- Internet/Web Technologies

ΔWARDS

- Graduated Summa Cum Laude (Arizona State University)
- Dean's List (Arizona State University)
- Dean's List (Illinois Institute of Technology)

LANGUAGES

- English (native)
- Spanish (conversational, literary)